Thank you for watching!
Idol Divine Voice Battle
In this program, two sparkling idol groups will put their pride on the line and go head-to-head!
They will show off their singing voices and decide which idol has the voice of God.
By the way, my name is Molly, an android dj from the near future, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen, for this exciting battle of vocal talents, we'd like to introduce to you our newest idol.
First of all, let's start with sq 48.
Yes, we are STU48. Please give them my best regards.
Please give them my best regards.
And now, here to compete with STU48 are the Fruit Zippers.
We are Fruit Zipper.
Please give us your best regards.
Click here to see the battle of the divine voices that you will be challenging this time.
Related Tan Karaoke
In "3 Rensoku Karaoke", 3 representatives from each group sing one song each and score each time. The game is cleared when the three singers are right.
If both teams are right or wrong, the total score of the three will be the group's score and the winner will be decided.
The singing ability is of course a must, but the management of who will sing among the members and what they will sing is also tested.
Do you understand, Mr. Sakurai?
Yes, I did.
You don't seem to have.
Please don't cheat with your heart.
By the way, the idol group that successfully wins the battle of the divine voices will receive a melon from Furano, Hokkaido.
Are you hungry, Fruit Zipper?
Melon what?
What? Mr. Nakagawa.
Meanwhile, I cut the melon myself.
I didn't know you could do that.
I'd like to have this precious melon today.
Yes, so I would like to ask you to do your best.
We have three songs from five different genres for you to sing.
This is a 20th century idol song, a 21st century idol song, a buzz song, a song from the other group, and a song from our own group.
It is very important to choose from this wide range of songs.
Let's discuss and decide who will sing which songs!
I'm already on the market to rave reviews!
STU team, you are getting applause!
Okay, I want to hear the ones we haven't sung much.Okay, I want to hear less singing.
The obvious voice, STU, have you decided yet?
Yes, we have.
Okay, first of all, I'd like you to decide who's going to go first and who's going to go second.
Any preference?
Second team, second team, second team.
Bruce Zipper, would you like to be on the back?
Yes, sir.
I definitely want Bruce Zipper on the back.
And how about STU?
Backwards.
Back of the line.
Let's see how it goes first.
What shall we do? Representative Rock-Paper-Scissors?
Matsukura, rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
You're in charge of rock-paper-scissors-paper?
I've never lost at rock-paper-scissors-paper.
You're lying!
Really? I'm sure.
Really?
Well, baby to baby.
Let's do it.
First, rounds of rock, paper, scissors.
Aiko, right? Aiko, right?
You're so strong!
The myth of corruption continues.
STU48 will go first.
Who will sing the first song?
Top butter, please.
Ishida, let's go.
Ishida.
Now, Ishida-san, the top batter, how do you feel on the stage? Do you feel nervous?
I am really nervous. Just a few dozen centimeters difference makes a real difference.
And another idol group is also watching you.
And they are closer. This one is closer.And it's closer. This way is closer.
It's closer. Yes, it is.
I'm nervous. I'm so nervous.
So, Mr. Ishida, where do you choose the genre of your music?
We choose our own songs.
That's good. That's great.
There are a lot of main songs, but what will you sing?
Yes, we will sing "Breathing Heart" by STU48.
Why did you choose this one?
Yes, this one is on sale now.
Yes, it's PR. It's very important.
I chose this song because I wanted many people to listen to it.
The center singer will be singing solo this time.
Are you ready for it?
Yes, I am.
Chiho Ishida will sing.
STU48 Breathe Your Heart
Performance in the studio
Midnight is my own time
I hope no one falls asleep anymore
I can be my true self and breathe
When the sun rises on the earth
When the sun rises and the earth is covered in light and shadow
And when I'm standing on the edge of it all
I can't catch my breath
Oh, in a dream, I'm free
I'm free in my dreams I'm free in my dreams I'm free in my dreams
There it is, a normal breath in and a normal breath out
I'm breathing in and out like a normal person I've fallen in love with you
My shoulders are relaxed I'm still me
I don't have to change.
I like you. I like you, too. I like you, too.
I'm gonna say it out loud. I like you. I like you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.It was a singing performance.
Mr. Ishida, how was it?
Well, I don't sing alone that often.
I was very nervous.
You were very nervous?
The calls of the members...
The calls...
When you came to the end...
It must have been very powerful.
I laughed.
So, how was everyone at STU?
Chiho's voice is so reassuring.
Chiho's voice makes me feel at ease.
It's so much fun to listen to.
I couldn't help but say the same thing.
By the way...
What do you think the score will be, Mr. Ishida?
I think it's quite difficult.
It's our own song.
I'd like to say 100 points.
It's good.
Eighty-two points.
Eighty-two.
I think you're being a little modest.
I don't think so.
Okay, 90 points.
Eight all the way up.
Who'll sing the second song?
Yes, Mr. Imamura.
Please come on stage.
How are you feeling? How do you feel now?
Well, it's not often that I get a chance to sing alone when I'm in a group, so I guess so. The floor is shining so brightly.
More than usual, that's for sure.
What genre would you choose?
Well, let's see, I'll start with 21st century idol songs.Yes, let's see, from the 21st Century Idol song.
Oh, that's nice.
The song is Hatsukoi Cider by GO!NO.
I like it.
I used to like idols a lot, and I used to listen to and sing Hatsukoi Cider a lot, so I thought I would give it a try.
I'll give you a KISS, I just realized.
I'll give you a KISS for the feelings I've just realized
Because any words are not enough
I'll give you KISS, the feelings I've just realized
It's so obvious
Because we've been friends for so long
I know your habits and personality
I know you better than the other kids
Oh, without childcare
I can't wait to see how shy you'll be
I can't wait to see you.
I'll give you a kiss.
I can't believe you like me now.
That's more than words can say
I'll tell you in secret, just for you
The warmth of a little bud deep in my chest
Thank you very much.
How was it singing?
I was so nervous.
Your voice came out.
Really?
I knew that Mr. Mitsch...
He's a member of ST48.
He was so steady.
ST48 usually has quite calm songs.
but "Hatsukoi Cider" made me feel so happy.
I fell in love with her cute voice even more!
I fell in love even more!
She was an idol!
They were idols!I was an idol.
You've reaffirmed it once again.
Who will be the last one?
Here it is, Mr. Ikeda!
Please come on stage!
How do you feel now?
Since it's my last time, I'd like to sing with all my might.
What genre should we choose?
I'd like to sing a buzz song.
A buzz song sounds good, doesn't it?
I'd like to sing "Adult Blue" by New School Leaders.
I'd like to sing "Adult Blue" by the New School Leaders.
That's great.
I've got so many cute people watching me.
I don't get a chance to do this.
I want to have fun.
Oh, my God.
He's too big.
Yura Ikeda will sing
New School Leaders
Adult Blue
Please subscribe to our channel!
I know, I know, you want it.
These lips are so glossy
Soft men, creatures to attract
The outrageously sweet nectar
I know you want it, I know you want it, I know you want it, I know you want it, I know you want it, I know you want it
Sweaty streets, walking alone, slutty eyes entwine
Hey, what do you expect?
I don't want it right away, I want it right now
I'm longing for a grown-up love that's more than meets the eye
Only the innocent heart is blooming and running, still a blue bud, adult blue
What's with you?
What's the matter with you?
I'm so proud of you!
Now it's time for the predictions!Now it's time to make your predictions!
Please predict your score and rank.
I want to eat a lot of melon, Mr. Nakagawa. I want to eat melon, too.
Let's hear your predictions for the STU teams.
Here they are!
First place goes to Yura Ikeda's "Adult Blue" Second place goes to Chiho Ishida's "Spirited Heart
Third place goes to Imamura's Hatsukoi Cider!
Ike-chan has a lot of points, I guess.
I took into account the tempo of the song and other various factors to come up with this ranking.
By the way, the Fruit Zipper team also made their predictions!
Here they are!
Ike 90, Mizuki 87, Chiho 86.
That's a pretty realistic guess!
Now let's see if our predictions were right!
Which STU team would you like to see first?
First place
I'll open with a solid first place.
Will they make it three in a row?
Time for destiny!
Here we go
STU48 No. 1 is...
92 points
Mizuki Imamura
Well, I'm delighted, but I'm disqualified.
This is a pretty blunt response. I'm stunned.
I guess Ms. Imamura is happy for Imamura, but feels awkward
Melon...
Well, let's announce them in order now, shall we?
Second place, 90 points
Yura Ikeda
I don't have any special preference.
Third place goes to Ishida-san, with 87 points.
I'm so disappointed about the melon... Everyone wanted a melon so badly!
The total score was 269 points.
If Fruit Zipper misses the trifecta, he will have to go over this point!
So thank you very much to everyone at STU48 for all your hard work!So, thank you very much to everyone at STU48 for your hard work!
And now, for our next trifecta of karaoke...
Coco Fruit Zipper's challenge!
Yay!
First, please raise your hands to indicate who will sing.
Yes, the three in the back row.
Now, who will be the top grasshopper?
Yes, sir.
I am Tsukitashi.
It is Mr. Tsukitashi.
Yay! It's Mr. Moonshine.
Go for it!
Then, please come up on stage.
Come on, Mr. Tsukihi. Which genre would you choose?
The other group's song.
I have a song that I like the most,
It's called "Darkness,
I'm going to sing that song today.
I'm very nervous,
I am very nervous,
It's the first time I'm going to sing it today.
It's my first time singing.
We have never seen another group sing our song in person,
I'm really honored and I'll do my best,
I feel honored and will do my best.
I'm very excited.
Tsukitashi Amane STU48
Darkness.
The sun is aiming beyond the horizon, Aloe listened to the dusk with a sense of depravity.
Is there no love like something left undone?
I don't want to go home yet
While being made to do what I want to do and what I don't want to do
The days when ideals and reality are mixed up
Just like the sky and the sea are divided
It means that there are things that do not intersectI mean, there are some things you just can't cross.
My friend who lives in the city seems to only see the window
When I'm lonely and I can't stand it
Who can I cry to?
Night, don't make me a poet
I don't want to end on a clean slate
I don't want to live, I don't want to be hurt
I want to be moist and ungraceful
Before the next morning comes
I'll throw away what I have
I'll find myself naked
In that darkness
If you look hard enough
You'll see something.
Thank you so much, I was so nervous.
After the song was over, I glanced at stu's voice and thought, "I like stu's voice better.
Buvershi, how much do you think the special was?
815 I hope so... I think I'm just saying that...
Who will sing "9 Dolls?" Yes, Mr. Nakagawa will sing.
Mr. Nakagawa will sing.
You don't look nervous. I'm not nervous.
It's hard to understand. What genre of song?
The 21st Century Idol by Mr. Bisch, "On a Starry Night"... a favorite of Mr. Bisch's.
Are you ready?
Runa Nakagawa to Bish, "The Night the Stars Blink.
This is a special episode.
Gods and Goddesses
Cherry Blossoms
Shika
full
polka dots
Cherry blossoms...
・・・・.
Chavi
cents
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, heyHey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Aqua ai, oh yeah, you never stop bluffing
This place on the first line is like a paradise
Mistakes students who are bad at arithmetic
Bad fights, calculator banging world
I'm a guest in a gin and tonic
How is an idol's life?
I gotta go, don't mind if I'm a monster
On a night when the stars are twinkling
Kill my face, it's so innocent
That's right. It's crazy how fast they decide.
Don't tell me you don't care that I'm a freak
On a night when the stars are twinkling
Kill my face I don't care if it's inside out or on the flip side
You're so quick to want it.
I'm just gonna say it.
Yay!
Yes, thank you very much!
Well, you sang spontaneously, Mr. Nakagawa.
This song is fun, isn't it?
You were having fun.
But, I don't know, STU sang along with us,
When I sang "aiyoi", they said "oiyoi" to me,
I was having a lot of fun.
Ms. Nakagawa, you talk a little too much with your senses.
Actually, it was her birthday yesterday,
Happy birthday!
Thank you very much!
It's amazing to see how much she has been reborn,
A new cell, a cell of fashion, was born.
Now, let's come to the last part of the show.
The last one is, of course, Mr. Sakurai.
Please come up to the stage.
Please come up on stage.
It's already the end.
Please don't say too much.Please don't say too much.
I beg your pardon.
Oh, I'm so nervous.
Nervous?
Yes, I am.
Which song would you like?
Let's see, I'll play 21st Century Idol.
Okay. What would you like to sing?
I'll choose Aya Matsuura's "Peach-colored unrequited love".
It's good.
Well, I like Hello Project.
I see.
Yes, I like Hello Project. So..,
Yes.
Memories,
Yes. It's a song.
Yes, sir.
Yui Sakurai, Aya Matsuura, Momoiro Katakami.
Aikuyo! One, two, three!
Yay!
Peach-colored one-sided love I'm in love
I'm staring at you so hard.
Glancing at each other, our eyes meet, our hearts are aching...
Peach-colored fantasy
Yay!
I've never had a one-sided love like this before.
It's like I love him so much that I don't know what I don't know.
I wonder if he has a girlfriend...
I wonder if he has a girlfriend.
I'm interested in him right now
I know about your peach-colored one-sided love
I know it before I know it
I met her by chance... My heart is pounding...
I'm in love with a peach-colored crushI have a peach-colored crush. I'm in love.
I'm staring at you, staring at you, staring at you.
When our eyes meet...
My heart is aching... Peach-colored fantasy...
Yes, thank you very much.
Well, I think you were perfect from the very beginning of the song.
It was a lot of fun, and all the members said they didn't like it.
Yes, it was so cute. It was like Yui's song.
The companion was too cute. He had it all to himself.
Now then, it's time for the predictions!
I don't know!
Now, please announce your predictions for the Fruit Zipper team.
Deden!
Yes, I'm Deden!
First place, Yui Chappie.
And in second place, Re-Nappi.
Third place goes to Tsukisoku.
I'm calling only Tsukisoku by its name.
Because the monthly foot is the monthly foot.
Tsukisoku is Tsukisoku.
Please announce the STU team.
This way, please.
Yes, this way.
Here we go.
First place, Amane Tsukisoku.
Second place, Yui Sakurai.
Third place, Rena Nakagawa.
But we were a little happy to have our song sung.
Yes, I was.
I put it at No. 1.
I see, so STU gets extra points.
That's right.
Now I would like to announce the ranking.
What rank would you like to see the Fruit Zipper team in?
Starting with 3rd place.
How many years will they achieve?Then how many years will be achieved?
Time for destiny.
Here we go!
Third place
Nakagawa Mana, 85.1 points
No full chinpachin, no melon.
I guess that means the overall score may be
STU team guessed it?
Will the STU team achieve three consecutive wins?
Second place, 85.6 points
Tsukisoku Abane
At this point, the STU team also failed to guess.
I'd like to announce the first place winner with a little upset that they didn't win the triple crown.
So, here is the winner!
88.0 points
Yui Sakurai
Since neither of the two teams predicted a triple tan, I'd like to decide the winner based on the overall score.
I would like to decide the winner based on the overall score
The STU team scored 269 points overall
The Fruit Zipper team scored 258 points overall
So, the winner is STU48!
STU48 will receive a Frano melon from Hokkaido!
Congratulations!
Here's a little melon for you!
What a wonderful story of friendship!
How was it, Mr. Ishida?
Yes, I'm very happy.
But I'm more sorry than happy.
It was a complicated game, wasn't it?
It was very complicated.
How was it, Mr. Hayase?
You were very good. Everyone was happy.
We're going to have a melon karaoke party with psylliums and stuff afterwards.
I want to have a melon karaoke party with psylliums and stuff!
I have a grand after-party planned!
So, that was the Idol God's Voice Battle!So, that's all for now, Idol God's Voice Battle!
See you next time!
We are anie day!
ana
th
ran